Oh, she's a blue-eyed angel.
I cannot deny I want her tonight.
When I look into her eyes, it feels like I'll never die.
Oh, she's a blue-eyed angel.
And I wonder at the world inside.
Her love burns me up.
Leaves me nothing left to hide.
She's a blue-eyed angel.
And I can't look away.
Every time she holds me, I lose another piece of yesterday.
Blue-eyed angel.
Oh, come and take me home.
I don't want to be alone.
If loving you is heaven.
Let me lose my way.
Blue-eyed angel.
Don't ever let me wait.
Oh, she's a blue-eyed angel.
Blue-eyed angel.
And I swear she pulls me in.
I want to crawl inside her.
And disappear beneath her skin.
When she whispered my name.
I forget where I've been.
She's a blue-eyed angel.
And I'd fall for her again.
Blue-eyed angel.
Oh, come and take me home.
I don't want to be alone.
Blue-eyed angel.
If loving you is heaven.
Then let me lose my way.
Blue-eyed angel.
Don't ever let me wait.
Don't let me go.
Blue-eyed angel.
Don't ever let me go.
I don't want to be alone.
If loving you is heaven.
Then let me lose my way.
Blue-eyed angel.
Don't ever let me wait.
Don't ever let me go.
Blue-eyed angel.
You're all I want to know.
When I look into your eyes.
I see forever there.
Blue-eyed angel.
I'll meet you anywhere.
Come take me home.
Blue-eyed angel.
Don't ever let me wait.
Blue-eyed angel